Guide to the Athletics and Recreation Department records, 1890-2009 RG0054
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- George Washington sports information collection, 1930-1993; RG0054 Series 1; 15 Linear feet (Box 6, Box 5, Box 11, Box 8, Box 10, Box 7, Box 9, Box 2, Box 1, Box 4, Box 3)
  - Basketball videotape - Rutgers game, first half, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Basketball videotape - Rutgers game, second half, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Basketball videotape - Penn State game, first half, 12/11/1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Basketball videotape - North Carolina State game [1/3], 12/11/1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Basketball videotape - North Carolina State game [2/3], 12/11/1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Basketball videotape - North Carolina State game [3/3], 12/11/1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Basketball videotape - Maryland game, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Basketball videotape - Georgtown game [1/2], 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Basketball videotape - Georgtown game [2/2], undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Basketball videotape - Monmouth game, first half, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Basketball videotape - Monmouth game, second half, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Basketball videotape - Navy game, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Basketball videotape - UB Invitational, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Basketball videotape - Karen Ballentine, All-American candidate, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Basketball videotape - Maryland game, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Basketball videotape - St. Mary's game, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Volleyball (?) videotape - game vs. Hofstra, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Videotape - unlabeled, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Rob Goodman's headset, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified sporting event - GW vs. Georgia Tech, [1/3], undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    7" reel to reel tapes
  - Unidentified sporting event - GW vs. Georgia Tech, [2/3], undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified sporting event - GW vs. Georgia Tech, [3/3], undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Button - "Score with Women's Athletics", undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    2 buttons
  - Button - "God bless you, Title IX", 1985 ca. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    3 buttons
  - Button - "Give Women a Sporting Chance", 1975 ca. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Tickets - various sporting events, 1979-1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Baseball uniform top, 1980 ca. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Pom pom, 1990 ca. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Colonials" foam hatchet, 1990 ca. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bumper sticker - "George Washington Women's Athletics", undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    3 bumper stickers
  - Bumper sticker - "Colonial Women", undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    6 bumper stickers
  - Bumper sticker - "Jumping to the Big Time", undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    2 bumper stickers
  - Bumper sticker - The Other Washington Monument - GW Basketball", undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Bumper sticker - "The New Washington Monument: GW Colonials", undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Bumper sticker - "Colonial Spirit - Women's Athletics", undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Bumper sticker - "Colonials Basketball", undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Bumper sticker - "GW Basketball with Coke", undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Bumper sticker - "The Sky's the Limit - Colonial Women", undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Basketball films, 1969-1981; RG0054 Series 2; 15 Linear feet
  This series consists of 16 mm basketball films. The materials range in date from 1969-81.
  Formerly ACC#101, formerly RG6.4
  - GWU vs. AU (#2), 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GWU vs. Villanova (#1), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown (#1), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - GWU vs. Duquesne (#2), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - GWU vs. American U (#1), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - GWU vs. Stetson (#2), 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. West Virginia (#1), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - GWU vs. Florida State (#1), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - GWU vs. AU (#1), 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. Maryland (#2), 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - GWU vs. Marshall (#1), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - GWU vs. Wm. & Mary (#2), 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - GWU vs. Wm. & Mary (#2), 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - GWU vs. Pitt (#1), 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown (#1), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - GWU vs. Villanova (#1), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - GWU vs. V.P.I. (#2), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - GWU vs. Massachusetts (#2), 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - GWU vs. Richmond (#2), 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - GWU vs. Rutgers (1st game) (#2), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. American U (#2), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - GWU vs. V.P.I. (#1), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - J.R. Black - "GW HiLites", 05/12/1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. Stetson (#1), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - GWU vs. Wisconsin (#1), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - GWU vs. Stetson (#2), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - GWU vs. Wisconsin (#2), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - GWU vs. Delaware (#1), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - GWU vs. Maryland (#1), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - GWU vs. Jacksonville (#2), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - GWU vs. Stetson (#1), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - GWU vs. Connecticut (#1), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - GWU vs. V.P.I. (#2), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - GWU vs. Navy (#1), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. Navy (#2), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - GWU vs. West Virginia (#1), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - GWU vs. Syracuse (#1), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. Villanova (#2), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - GWU vs. West Virginia (#2) (Second Game of Season), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - GWU vs. Penn State (#2) (Presidential Classic finals), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown (#2), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - GWU vs. Connecticut (#2), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - GWU vs. Marshall (#2) (Game 2), 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - GWU vs. Delaware (#1), 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - GWU vs. Duquesne (#1), 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - GWU vs. West Virginia (#2), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - GWU vs. UMass (#1), 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. Villanova (#2), 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - GWU vs. American U. (#1), 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - GWU vs. Villanova (#2), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. Duquesne (#1), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - GWU vs. UMass (#2), 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - [Illegable], 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - GWU vs. V.P.I. (#1), 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - GWU vs. St. Peters (#1), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - GWU vs. Syracuse (#2), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - GWU vs. UMass (#2), 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - GWU vs. Jacksonville (#1), 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Rutgers, Duquesne (#2), 02/25/1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - (#2) GW - '67, MD - '69, 01/23/1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - (#1) GW - '67, MD - '69, 01/23/1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - GW vs. Georgetown (#2), undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - GW vs. Georgetown (#3), undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - (#3) GW - '67, MD - '69, 01/23/1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. Rutgers (#2), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - GW vs. Georgetown 1 of 4, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - GWU vs. St. Bonaventure (#1), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. St. Bonaventure (#2), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - GWU vs. St. Bonaventure (#3), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - GWU vs. St. Bonaventure (#4), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Rutgers, Duquesne (#3), 02/25/1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - GWU vs. Rutgers (#1), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rutgers, Duquesne (#1), 02/25/1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - GWU vs. Rutgers (#3), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - GWU vs. Rutgers (#4), 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - U of Utah training film - black and white offense - Gerry Gimelstob's copy, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - GW vs. Georgetown 2 of 4, 04/09/1969 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - "Savor" ... Cincinnati, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - GWU vs. Dequesne (#2), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - GWU vs. Syracuse (#1), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - GWU vs. Boston U. (#1), 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - DUQ, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - DUQ, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - GWU vs. Delaware (#2), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. Maryland (#2), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - GWU vs. Massachusetts (#1), 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - GWU vs. Rutgers (#2), 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. West Virginia (#2), 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Untitled (#2), undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - GWU vs. Florida State (#2), 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - GWU vs. Rutgers (#1), 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - GWU vs. Villanova (#1), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown (#2), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - GWU vs. Richmond (#1), 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - GWU vs. Boston U. (#2), 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Carl Slone - Team Defense, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Carl Slone - Running Game - Faster, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - GWU vs. Richmond (#1), 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - GWU vs. William & Mary (#1), 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - GWU vs. Richmond (#2), 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. St. Peters (#1), 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - GWU vs. St. Peters (#2), 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. U.Mass (#1), 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - GWU vs. Richmond (#1), undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - GWU vs. West Virginia (#1), 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - GWU vs. Penn State (#1) (Presidential Classic Championship), 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - GWU vs. Delaware (#2), 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - GWU vs. Maryland (#1), 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - GWU vs. William & Mary (#1), 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown ((#1)), 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown (#2), 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - GWU vs. Pitt, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - GWU vs. American U. (#1), 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - GWU vs. American U. (#2), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - GWU vs. American U. (#2), 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. Rutgers (#1) (first game), 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - GWU vs. St. Peters (#2), 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - GWU vs. Pitt (#2), 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown (#1), 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - GWU vs. Maryland (#1), 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - GWU vs. Cincinnati, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown (#2), 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown (#2), 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 2 reels, untitled, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - GWU vs. Georgetown, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - GWU vs. Pittsburgh, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - GWU vs. Maryland, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - GWU vs. West Virginia, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - GWU vs. American U. (Presidential Classic), 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - GWU vs. Long Island U., 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "GW Hi-Lightz-1976", 04/06/1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - GWU vs. American U. (#1), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - GWU vs. American U. (#2), 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - GWU vs. Pitt (#1), 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Athletics Communications Office files and publications, 1972-2011; RG0054 Series 3; 13 Linear Feet
  This series contains publications produced by the Athletics Communications Office (also known as the Sports Information Office), including sports media guides and programs. Sports include crew, women's gymnastics, women's volleyball, men's basketball, women's basketball, baseball, men's soccer, women's soccer, men's tennis, women's tennis, men's water polo, women's water polo, lacrosse, softball, cross country, swimming and diving, and men's golf. The series also contains women's athletic public relations notebooks, sports information notebook, notebook on association for intercollegiate athletics for women, and Hatchets. Materials date from 1979 to 2011.
  Includes ACC#185; formerly RG6.4
  - Men's Basketball, 1972-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Media guides, game programs, pre-season prospectuses, post-season guides
  - Women's Basketball, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Media guides, pre-season prospectuses, post-season guides, Atlanitc 10 Championship programs
  - All-Sports Media Guide, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Baseball, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Media guides, Atlantic 10 Tournament guides
  - Crew, 1986-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Media guides, Crew Classic/Cherry Blossom programs
  - Cross Country Guide, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Gymnastics, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Media guides, 1991 Atlantic 10 program
  - Men's Soccer Media Guides, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Women's Soccer Media Guides, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Swimming and Diving Media Guides, 1985-1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Tennis Media Guides, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Volleyball, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Media guides, game programs, Atlantic 10 programs
  - Water Polo Media Guides, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Wrestling Media Guides, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Team Schedules, 1984-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - GW Athletics Articles, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Primarily on men's basketball
  - "Interesting Articles" Notebook, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Does not pertain directly to GW Athletics
  - "Public Relations" Notebook, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Articles, game/championship programs for women's athletics
  - Public Relations Notebooks, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Articles, game & championship programs for women's athletics
  - Budget and Expense Notebook for Women's Athletics, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sports Information Notebook for Women's Athletics, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Atlantic 10 Memos, Meetings, Info., Letters, etc., 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic 10 Memos, Meetings, Info., Letters, Propsals, etc., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Sports Medicine Information, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Notebook on Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nat'l. AIAW Badminton Tournament Notebook, 03/1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - GW Hatchets, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Not in order; contains scattered '91-'93 issues
  - GW Hatchets, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Not in order; contains scattered '89-'90 issues
  - Basketball Schedules, 2008-2009 card, magnets, clingz, 1944-2009; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 1)
  - Basketball yearbook 2008-2009 game program, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball 2008-2009 Media Guide, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball 2008-2009 Media Guide, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 4)
  - Volleyball Media Guide 2008, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 5)
  - Soccer Media Guides 2008, Men's and Women's, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 6)
  - Baseball Media Guides 2009, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 7)
  - Rowing Programs 2009, Invitational Regatta, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball Post-Season A-10 Tournament Guides 2009, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 9)
  - Softball Media Guides 2009, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 10)
  - Golf Media Guides 2008-2009, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 11)
  - Swimming Media Guides 2008-2009 Men's and Women's, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 12)
  - Cross Country Media Guides 2008 Men's and Women's, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 13)
  - Gymnastics Media Guides 2009, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 14)
  - Women's Lacrosse Media Guides 2009, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 15)
  - Rowing Media Guides 2008-2009, Men's and Women's, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 16)
  - Tennis Media Guides 2008-2009 Men's and Women's, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 17)
  - Water Polo Media Guides 2008-2009, Men's and Women's, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 18)
  - Squash Media Guides 2008-2009 Men's and Women's, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 19)
  - Basketball Programs 1996-1997, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 20)
  - Basketball Programs 1995-1996, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 21)
  - Basketball Programs 1994-1995, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 22)
  - Basketball Programs 1993-1994, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 23)
  - Basketball Programs 1992-1993, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 25)
  - Basketball Programs 1990-1991, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 26)
  - Basketball Programs 1989-1990, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 27)
  - Basketball Programs 1988-1989, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 28)
  - Basketball Programs 1987-1988, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 29)
  - Basketball Programs 1986-1987, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 30)
  - Basketball Programs 1984-1985, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 31)
  - Basketball Programs 1982-1983, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 32)
  - Colonials Insider Athletic Department Newsletters 1999-2007, 01/1999-06/2007; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 33)
  - GW Magazine Spring/Summer 2006, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 34)
  - GW Hatchet, 07/14/1988; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 35)
  - Photos, Women's Basketball Alumnae, circa 1986; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 36)
  - Assorted Athletics Photos, circa 1989; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 37)
  - Women's Athletic Association Bookeeping Journal, 1944; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 38)
  - GW Baseball Alumni Photo, circa 1989; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 39)
  - GW Guide to Alumni Benefits and Services, 1999-2000; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 40)
  - Women's Basketball 2004 NCAA Tournament Post-Season Guides, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 41)
  - Women's Basketball 2003 NCAA Tournament Post-Season Guide, RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 42)
  - GW Viewbook, 1989; RG0054 Series 3 (Box SERIES 3 BOX 8, Folder 43)
  - Baseball scorecard -- GW Colonials vs. St. Joseph's Hawks, 03/22/2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Men's and Women's Tennis Media Guides, 2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Men's and Women's Rowing Media Guides, 2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Men's and Women's Water Polo Media Guides, 2007-2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cross Country Media Guides, 2007; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Swimming and Diving Media Guides, 2007-2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Men's Golf Media Guides, 2007-2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lacrosse Media Guides, 2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Softball Media Guides, 2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Women's Gymnastics Media Guides, 2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Men's and Women's Soccer Media Guides, 2007; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Women's Volleyball Media Guides, 2007; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Baseball Media Guides, 2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball Media Guide, 2007-2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball Media Guides, 2007-2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball Postseason Media Guides, 2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Men's and Women's Rowing, 21st George Washington Invitational Regatta program, 04/11/2008-04/12-2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Schedules and Magnets, 2007-2008; Series 3 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Baseball 2010 Media Guides, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball 2009-10 Media Guides, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball 2009-10 Media Guides, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Basketball 2009-10 Yearbooks (game programs), 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country 2009 Recruiting Brochures, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Men's Golf 2009-10 Media Guides, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Women's Gymnastics 2010 Media Guides, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Women's Lacrosse 2010 Media Guides, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Men's Rowing 2009-10 Recruiting Brochures, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Women's Rowing 2009-10 Recruiting Brochures, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Men's Soccer 2009 Media Guides, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Women's Soccer 2009 Media Guides, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Softball 2010 Media Guides, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Men's and Women's Squash 2009-10 Recruiting Brochures, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Men's and Women's Swimming 2009-10 Recruiting Brochures, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Men's Tennis 2009-10 Recruiting Brochures, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Women's Tennis 2009-10 Recruiting Brochures, 2009-2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Volleyball 2009 Media Guides, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Men's Water Polo 2009 Recruiting Brochures, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Women's Water Polo 2010 Recruiting Brochures, Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Invitational Rowing Regatta Programs April 9-10, 2010, 9 April, 2010-10 April, 2010; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - George Washington Basketball Yearbook, Vol. 1, 2010-2011; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - George Washington Basketball Yearbook, Vol. 2, 2010-2011; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - EAGL Gymnastics Championships program, 19 March 2011; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Newspaper clippings, 1983-1990; RG0054 Series 4; 3 Linear feet
  This series contains sports information newspaper clippings.
  This material was donated by the GW Sports Information Program.
  The material ranges in date from 1983-90.
  Formerly ACC#193, formerly RG6.4
  This series has a paper container list in the reading room, please ask staff for assistance.
- Videotapes, 1986-1994; RG0054 Series 5; 6 Linear feet
  This series contains women's basketball video tapes, Coach Mike Jarvis' show tapes.
  The material was donated by the GW Sports Information Program.
  The material ranges in date from 1986-94.
  Formerly ACC#219, formerly RG6.4
  This series has a container list in electronic form, please ask staff for assistance.
- Uniforms, ca.1980-ca.1990; RG0054 Series 6; 4.5 Linear feet
  This series contains old uniforms from the Athletic Department. They range in date from ca.1980-ca.1990. This material was donated by the GW Sports Information Program.
  Formerly ACC#233, formerly RG6.4
- Certificate and photograph, 1956-1987; RG0054 Series 7; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of a certificate of appreciation for varsity football team (1956) and a framed photo with Steve Bilsky, Serge Gambol, and John Kuester (1987).
  The materials range in date from 1956 for the certificate and 1987 for the photograph.
  Formerly ACC#594, formerly RG6.4
- Newspaper clippings, 1995; RG0054 Series 8; 0.5 Linear foot
  This series consists of newspaper clippings about GW's upset of University of Massachussetts in basketball on February 5, 1995.
  Formerly ACC#339, formerly RG6.4